If this is your first Nanodegree program, you start here.
If you've taken a Nanodegree program with us before,
you already know a little bit of what to expect.
Udacity is always improving our learning experience for students.
So you can watch this to see what has changed or you can skip ahead.
You can also download the transcript of this video in the resources tab.
Let's get started. We truly believe that
you couldn't have chosen a better place to learn.
A lot of people have worked tirelessly to create
the course material and platform features,
as we all want you to get the most of your learning journey.
Our pledge is to provide you with resources and
services that will further enable you to succeed in your Nanodegree program.
As you go through the lessons,
you may find some to be difficult and may feel discouraged.
If this happens, we encourage you to take advantage of
your community channels and mentor services to help clarify the concepts,
or just to share your doubts.
Our mentors are there to help you.
You will get advice and guidance to ensure
that you are on track to complete the projects.
We want you to succeed and graduate with the Udacity Nanodegree certificate.
We value the trust you have put in us by making this investment in your future career.
We take it very seriously and we're here to help
you achieve whatever you came here to accomplish.